[Music]
hello
my name is cynician winda a financial
consultant at prudential life assurance
i have been with prudential over two
years six months in my time with
prudential i've had the
opportunity to meet and interact with
over a thousand clients and i've been
able to close over 550 cases
so what has kept me going in prudential
life assurance is the fact that i've
been given an opportunity
to be able to offer a service to my
clients i'm able to help my clients plan
for their finances
their children's future school fees as
well as their future investment
prudential has been very rewarding when
it comes to hard work i have received
recognition for every quest i have
closed hence making me one of the top
sales consultants
what makes me one of the top source
consultants is of course the hard work
that i put in
the discipline and the dedication in
sales of course you need to be
self-driven
self-motivated not only that i've also
taken ownership of the brand
the flexibility of the job has allowed
me to set personal targets for this year
both on the financial and on the
business front
so my encouragement to you who would
like to join prudential family
is your welcome this place allows you to
develop and sharpen your sales skill
and to everybody else who's already part
of the brand is it's possible to be
number one
through discipline determination and
hard work